{"data":[{"question":"The activities of the Tennessee Valley Authority have aided the economic rehabilitation of the Tennessee Valley, ___ of some 40,000 square miles.","a":"an area","b":"its area","c":"area","d":"areas","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- We haven't mention \"area\" before-> not determine yet=> use \"a, an\"\n\n- Use is a vowel=> an","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"How old is he? \" ___ \"","a":"He is thirty-four years","b":"He has thirty-four","c":"He is thirty-four years old","d":"He is thirty-four old","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Number + year (s) old: to show how old is someone","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"How about the walls? \"The walls are ___ thick.\"","a":"third inches","b":"three inches","c":"three inch","d":"third inch","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Number + unit + thick: to express how thick something is \n- Plural: Inch- inches ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"What authors do you like?  \"Hemingway is ___\"","a":"favorite for me","b":"the favorite of mines","c":"for me the favorite","d":"my favorite","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- My favorite = My favorite author = The favorite of mine","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Would you like to hear classical music or contemporary music? \"Classical music is my ___\"","a":"preferring","b":"preference","c":"one preferring","d":"one prefer","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- My\/his\/her...+ noun\/noun phrase\n\n- Preference is noun of verb \"prefer\"\n\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"He had to balance his account very carefully because he had ___.","a":"a few moneys","b":"few moneys","c":"little money","d":"a little money","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Money: uncoutable noun, therefore not plus \"s\" in plural\n\n-a little = some\n\n-little = hardly any","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"___ police were acting upon the information they received.","a":"The","b":"Many","c":"Much","d":"Little","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The police: the official organization whose job is to catch criminals and make sure that people obey the law \n- Police\/the police: always is plural and countable noun","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The victim of the accident sued the bus company for ___.","a":"the damage","b":"a damage","c":"damages","d":"damage","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n-Damages [plural] law money that a court orders someone to pay to someone else as a punishment for harming them or their property ? compensation","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The representatives of the party took great ___ in reaching a final agreement.","a":"a pain","b":"pains","c":"pain","d":"the pain","answer":"2","explain":"\n-Take\/go to (great) pains to do something (also take pains with\/over something)CAREFUL to make a special effort to do something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"___ is one of my favorite subjects.","a":"A mathematic","b":"The mathematic","c":"The mathematics","d":"Mathematics","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Mathematics: name of a science subject \n- General speaking: no need a\/the","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}